## **JOHN NEAGOE**

Toronto, ON L4E 5B3

E-mail: johnnyneagoe@gmail.com | Phone: (647) 801 6102

Portfolio: <a href="https://johnnyneagoe.github.io/My-Portfolio/">https://johnnyneagoe.github.io/My-Portfolio/</a> | LinkedIn: <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/johnnyneagoe">https://www.linkedin.com/in/johnnyneagoe</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/JohnnyNeagoe

Web Developer with extensive experience coding interactive websites and apps using industry leading techniques. Developed advanced critical thinking abilities, polished communication skills and a strong work ethic through a full-stack certification completed at UofT, prior employment experiences in management and acquiring an HBBA.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- JavaScript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, jQuery, React, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Firebase, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, Media Queries, APIs, REST, Handlebars, AJAX, the command line, computer science fundamentals.
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook); Microsoft Office Specialist Certification.

### **HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS**

## • Star Wars RPG Game

Link: <a href="https://johnnyneagoe.github.io/StarWars-Game/">https://johnnyneagoe.github.io/StarWars-Game/</a>

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and jQuery
- Description: Star Wars themed RPG game utilizing JavaScript & jQuery to make all calculations needed for user functionality and to listen to events such as beginning the game or choosing a character.

## Travel Itinerary Website:

Link: https://johnnyneagoe.github.io/WanderLust/

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, APIs, Client-Side Storage, Bootstrap
- Description: Travel App using google API to acquire user location and destination in order to efficiently provide valuable information in a clean and robust manor and give them the ability to choose bookings.

## Social Networking App for Neighborhoods

- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PassportJS, Google API, MySQL, Sequalize, ExpressJS, NodeJS
- Description: App designed for neighbourhoods, giving users the ability to easily interact with their fellow community members.
  Link <a href="https://hi-neighbour.herokuapp.com/dashboard">https://hi-neighbour.herokuapp.com/dashboard</a>

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## • LiVante Developments *Project Accountant*

Toronto ON June 2017 – Present

- Improved the efficiency of the accounting system, through the timely requirement of all necessary paperwork from other key departments and clients / vendors.
- Decreased expenditure by effectively implementing contractual obligations & negotiating additional work on a case by case basis.
- Enriched productivity of construction processes through implementing a robust purchase order system.
- Developed strong relationships with executives and other employees, allowing for swift conflict resolution, increased productivity and an overall improvement in communication.

## Mattamy Homes *Junior Financial Analyst*

Vaughan ON March 2017 – May 2017

- Enriched the efficiency of the reporting team by assisting with the creation of monthly financial reporting packages.
- Enhanced productivity in converting to a new enterprise system planning software (JDE) through multiple account analyses, resulting in the reclassification of accounts from one system to another.
- Established a strong understanding of the company environment and an ability distinguish between different types of contracts such as Joint Venture agreements.

# Greenwin Inc. & Johnson Insurance Inc. - Summer Internships Toronto / Newmarket, ON Junior Financial Analyst - 2015 & Accounting Analyst - 2014 & Claims Assistant - 2013

- Elevated comprehension of company financial growth and stability through the analysis of revenue, operating expenses and profit on a year-over-year and quarter-to-quarter basis.
- Perfected communication between account managers, vice president and director of finance through prompt reporting & administrative task completion.
- Amplified interdepartmental productivity through the implementation of a purchase order tracking system.
- Provided top-quality customer service while developing close relationships with insurance adjusters, which allowed for efficient and prompt assistance throughout the entire work term.

#### **EDUCATION**

## • Full Stack Web Development Certificate

- University of Toronto, St. George Campus

### Honours Bachelor of Business Administration

**September 2012 – May 2016** 

May 2018 - November 2018

- Wilfrid Laurier University, Waterloo Ontario
- Finance Major Economics Minor